<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="io.snyk.scanner"
      label="Snyk Security"
      version="3.7.0.qualifier"
      provider-name="Snyk">

   <description url="https://snyk.io">
      Secure development for developers and teams

    Snyk Security finds and fixes security vulnerabilities and infrastructure misconfigurations
    in your projects early in the development lifecycle to help you ace your security reviews and avoid a costly fix
    later down the line. If you’re an individual developer, open-source contributor, or maintainer at a large organization,
    Snyk helps you ship secure code, faster.

    Security for your entire application
    Comprehensive security for proprietary code, open-source dependencies, and infrastructure as code (IaC)
    configurations—all in one plugin. Whether you’re looking for a Java vulnerability scanner, a custom code
    vulnerability scanner, or open-source security scanner, or an application security plugin.

    Fast, free and accurate results
    Get security analysis of your code, and configurations free of charge. Snyk scans for vulnerabilities
    and misconfigurations in seconds. When returning your results, Snyk Security categorizes security issues by issue
    type and severity.
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0">
      Copyright 2019-2022 Snyk Limited
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0">
      Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the &amp;quot;License&amp;quot;);
    you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
    You may obtain a copy of the License at

    http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

    Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
    distributed under the License is distributed on an &amp;quot;AS IS&amp;quot; BASIS,
    WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
    See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
    limitations under the License.
   </license>

   <plugin
         id="io.snyk.eclipse.plugin"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
